<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GFG | NestedScrollView </string>

    <string name="random_text_1">Started several mistake joy say painful removed reached end. State burst think end are its. Arrived off she elderly beloved him affixed noisier yet. An course regard to up he hardly. View four has said does men saw find dear shy. Talent men wicket add garden.

He an thing rapid these after going drawn or. Timed she his law the spoil round defer. In surprise concerns informed betrayed he learning is ye. Ignorant formerly so ye blessing. He as spoke avoid given downs money on we. Of properly carriage shutters ye as wandered up repeated moreover. Inquietude attachment if ye an solicitude to. Remaining so continued concealed as knowledge happiness. Preference did how expression may favourable devonshire insipidity considered. An length design regret an hardly barton mr figure.

Raising say express had chiefly detract demands she. Quiet led own cause three him. Front no party young abode state up. Saved he do fruit woody of to. Met defective are allowance two perceived listening consulted contained. It chicken oh colonel pressed excited suppose to shortly. He improve started no we manners however effects. Prospect humoured mistress to by proposal marianne attended. Simplicity the far admiration preference everything. Up help home head spot an he room in.

As collected deficient objection by it discovery sincerity curiosity. Quiet decay who round three world whole has mrs man. Built the china there tried jokes which gay why. Assure in adieus wicket it is. But spoke round point and one joy. Offending her moonlight men sweetness see unwilling. Often of it tears whole oh balls share an.

Fulfilled direction use continual set him propriety continued. Saw met applauded favourite deficient engrossed concealed and her. Concluded boy perpetual old supposing. Farther related bed and passage comfort civilly. Dashwoods see frankness objection abilities the. As hastened oh produced prospect formerly up am. Placing forming nay looking old married few has. Margaret disposed add screened rendered six say his striking confined.

She travelling acceptance men unpleasant her especially entreaties law. Law forth but end any arise chief arose. Old her say learn these large. Joy fond many ham high seen this. Few preferred continual sir led incommode neglected. Discovered too old insensible collecting unpleasant but invitation.

Greatest properly off ham exercise all. Unsatiable invitation its possession nor off. All difficulty estimating unreserved increasing the solicitude. Rapturous see performed tolerably departure end bed attention unfeeling. On unpleasing principles alteration of. Be at performed preferred determine collected. Him nay acuteness discourse listening estimable our law. Decisively it occasional advantages delightful in cultivated introduced. Like law mean form are sang loud lady put.

Prepared do an dissuade be so whatever steepest. Yet her beyond looked either day wished nay. By doubtful disposed do juvenile an. Now curiosity you explained immediate why behaviour. An dispatched impossible of of melancholy favourable. Our quiet not heart along scale sense timed. Consider may dwelling old him her surprise finished families graceful. Gave led past poor met fine was new.

Respect forming clothes do in he. Course so piqued no an by appear. Themselves reasonable pianoforte so motionless he as difficulty be. Abode way begin ham there power whole. Do unpleasing indulgence impossible to conviction. Suppose neither evident welcome it at do civilly uncivil. Sing tall much you get nor.

Bringing unlocked me an striking ye perceive. Mr by wound hours oh happy. Me in resolution pianoforte continuing we. Most my no spot felt by no. He he in forfeited furniture sweetness he arranging. Me tedious so to behaved written account ferrars moments. Too objection for elsewhere her preferred allowance her. Marianne shutters mr steepest to me. Up mr ignorant produced distance although is sociable blessing. Ham whom call all lain like.

</string>

   <string name="random_text_2">Far quitting dwelling graceful the likewise received building. An fact so to that show am shed sold cold. Unaffected remarkably get yet introduced excellence terminated led. Result either design saw she esteem and. On ashamed no inhabit ferrars it ye besides resolve. Own judgment directly few trifling. Elderly as pursuit at regular do parlors. Rank what has into fond she.

But why smiling man her imagine married. Chiefly can man her out believe manners cottage colonel unknown. Solicitude it introduced companions inquietude me he remarkably friendship at. My almost or horses period. Motionless are six terminated man possession him attachment unpleasing melancholy. Sir smile arose one share. No abroad in easily relied an whence lovers temper by. Looked wisdom common he an be giving length mr.

Mind what no by kept. Celebrated no he decisively thoroughly. Our asked sex point her she seems. New plenty she horses parish design you. Stuff sight equal of my woody. Him children bringing goodness suitable she entirely put far daughter.

Unpleasant nor diminution excellence apartments imprudence the met new. Draw part them he an to he roof only. Music leave say doors him. Tore bred form if sigh case as do. Staying he no looking if do opinion. Sentiments way understood end partiality and his.

Frankness applauded by supported ye household. Collected favourite now for for and rapturous repulsive consulted. An seems green be wrote again. She add what own only like. Tolerably we as extremity exquisite do commanded. Doubtful offended do entrance of landlord moreover is mistress in. Nay was appear entire ladies. Sportsman do allowance is september shameless am sincerity oh recommend. Gate tell man day that who.

Passage its ten led hearted removal cordial. Preference any astonished unreserved mrs. Prosperous understood middletons in conviction an uncommonly do. Supposing so be resolving breakfast am or perfectly. Is drew am hill from mr. Valley by oh twenty direct me so. Departure defective arranging rapturous did believing him all had supported. Family months lasted simple set nature vulgar him. Picture for attempt joy excited ten carried manners talking how. Suspicion neglected he resolving agreement perceived at an.

He as compliment unreserved projecting. Between had observe pretend delight for believe. Do newspaper questions consulted sweetness do. Our sportsman his unwilling fulfilled departure law. Now world own total saved above her cause table. Wicket myself her square remark the should far secure sex. Smiling cousins warrant law explain for whether.

Pleased him another was settled for. Moreover end horrible endeavor entrance any families. Income appear extent on of thrown in admire. Stanhill on we if vicinity material in. Saw him smallest you provided ecstatic supplied. Garret wanted expect remain as mr. Covered parlors concern we express in visited to do. Celebrated impossible my uncommonly particular by oh introduced inquietude do.

Denote simple fat denied add worthy little use. As some he so high down am week. Conduct esteems by cottage to pasture we winding. On assistance he cultivated considered frequently. Person how having tended direct own day man. Saw sufficient indulgence one own you inquietude sympathize.

Effects present letters inquiry no an removed or friends. Desire behind latter me though in. Supposing shameless am he engrossed up additions. My possible peculiar together to. Desire so better am cannot he up before points. Remember mistaken opinions it pleasure of debating. Court front maids forty if aware their at. Chicken use are pressed removed.

</string>



</resources>